<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<diff>
	<add sel="/language">
		<page id="444750" title="Tyr" descr="Tyr" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">Tyr</t>
			<t id="2">(Tyr){20101,65301}</t>
			<t id="3">The Tyr-class battleship of the AGI Task Force was once the heavy weapons platform of the Earth Fleet, capable of leveling entire Xenon stations and capital ships of its time. Decommissioned along with several ships of the USC and ATF, its role was taken over by its successor - the Asgard-class battleship.\n\nAmidst the Jump Gate shutdown and the founding of the Terran Protectorate, a contingent of Terran military engineers banded together to update several USC/ATF designs to modern standards, with the Tyr having its vertical-facing turrets replaced with modular medium turrets, and also seeing a dramatic increase in size at the cost of maneuverability to capture the intimidating force projection of the Terrans.\n\nAlthough the blueprint was finished and approved, the Protectorate decided to keep deploying the Asgard due to its flexibility in the new theater of war and lower operating cost. On the other hand, pilots in good standing with the Protectorate are able to obtain a copy of the blueprint for a hefty sum.</t>
			<t id="4">IG XL - Tyr Internal Generator</t>
		</page>
		<page id="444751" title="Valhalla" descr="Valhalla" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">Valhalla</t>
			<t id="2">(Valhalla){20101,65401}</t>
			<t id="3">One of the biggest ships in the known universe, the Valhalla doubled as the AGI Task Force's flagship and command center. Easily dwarfing every other battleship of the Commonwealth and even the Xenon of its time, its presence alone was greatly feared by the enemies of Earth, not to mention its various capabilities. It was once said that the Valhalla knows everything that moves in Terran space... until the Torus Incident occurred. That, the Jump Gate shutdown, and the restructuring of the Terran military would eventually see the platform retired from service.\n\nSeveral Terran admirals have contested the decommissioning of the ship, seeing it too valuable to put out of the picture simply. While debates on whether the ship should be put back into service were happening, veteran ATF shipwrights covertly worked on overhauling the aging Valhalla to modern standards to sway the opinion of the higher-ups, upgrading it with massive shield and weapon generators that would allow the ship to serve as a mobile stronghold. When rumors broke out about the updated Valhalla years later, the Protectorate had already approved the blueprint but had not yet decided whether it should be redeployed.\n\nThe ship is so massive that the Terrans have devised its own unique "XXL-sized" multipurpose bay, the only place where the Valhalla can safely dock and perform repairs/upgrades. Such power comes with great responsibility and cost, and as such, only the closest allies of Earth are welcome to try and construct one of their own if they are willing to make a significant "donation" to the Terran cause.</t>
			<t id="4">IG XXL - Valhalla Internal Generator</t>
			<t id="5">Valhalla Fabrication Bay</t>
			<t id="6">Magni M/AM Drive</t>
			<t id="7">Valhalla Flagship</t>
			<t id="8">(Valhalla Flagship){20101,65401} {20204,6201}</t>
		</page>
		<page id="444752" title="Kyoto" descr="Kyoto" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">Kyoto</t>
			<t id="2">(Kyoto){20101,60301}</t>
			<t id="3">Deployed by the United Space Command at the apex of the Terran Conflict, the Kyoto was the USC's premier capital ship, a counterpart to their sister service's Valhalla. Bolstering a sheer-but-sleek design, the Kyoto maintains a small broadside profile, allowing its turrets' line of fire to be larger than most ships of its class while also being harder to hit.\n\nOver the years following the gate shutdown, the design was then improved upon during their isolation. Outfitted with classified engine housing technology as well as several changes to its carrier capabilities, the Kyoto was redesigned to be a rapid-response battlecarrier allowing it to achieve incredible speeds for its size as well as deploy entire fighter squadrons at a moment's notice without sacrificing an inch of its anti-capital ship capabilities.\n\nThere are rumors that the ship was never decommissioned - that it is merely being upgraded constantly due to the sudden rise in Terran breakthroughs, although the Protectorate has no comment on the matter. The blueprints of an older version, however, are available to the closest allies of Earth, under close watch by High Command.</t>
			<t id="4">IG XXL - Kyoto Internal Generator</t>
		</page>
		<page id="444753" title="Aegir" descr="Aegir" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">Aegir</t>
			<t id="2">(Aegir){20101,65501}</t>
			<t id="3">Once the standard heavy frigate of the AGI Task Force, the Aegir played an essential role in the Terran's counter-AGI effort and later on, the conflict between the Community of Planets. Due to advancements with the M7C frigates, the Aegir was eventually decommissioned after the development of the Falx-class frigate, carrying the features of both the M7 and M7C.\n\nA certain Terran PMC specializing in deep-space operations sought a ship design that would bridge the gap between frigate and destroyer and the Aegir's design fit the specifications perfectly. Upgraded for the current era, it features heavier weaponry and more powerful internal systems allowing it to take on a wide range of targets - from heavy fighters to light destroyers. Although originally unsanctioned by the Protectorate, several agreements took place and the ship was considered eligible for sale to pilots with sufficient privileges on their shipyards.</t>
			<t id="4">IG L - Aegir Internal Generator</t>
		</page>
		<page id="444754" title="Skirnir" descr="Skirnir" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">Skirnir</t>
			<t id="2">(Skirnir){20101,65601}</t>
			<t id="3">A legendary ship once known for singlehandedly deciding the outcome of a battle through sheer missile barrages, the M7M Skirnir of the AGI Task Force was a highly controversial ship among the Community of Planets as it could destroy entire sectors with the Terran-made Shadow Missiles of the time, which some captains of the USC and ATF had no problem using against the Argon primarily at the height of the Terran Conflict.\n\nWhen the gates re-opened, the need for such a heavy missile warship was not seen due to the relatively peaceful setting. Despite this, the Terrans, having endured the AGI attack and the destruction of the Torus Aeternal by the Argons, have devised a comprehensive contingency plan. For this purpose, the Skirnir, long decommissioned, was used as a platform and received an overhaul, effectively turning it into a heavy missile destroyer. Along with upgrades to its aging missile barrage system, the Skirnir was retrofitted with the latest components designed to balance out its role as a missile destroyer, dedicated to engaging capital ships and stations at a range with heavy warheads.</t>
			<t id="4">IG L - Skirnir Internal Generator</t>
			<t id="5">ATF Skirnir TACMS</t>
			<t id="6">ATF Skirnir Tactical Missile System</t>
			<t id="7">Laevateinn Multi-Missile</t>
			<t id="8">Considered to be the spiritual successor to the old Terran Shadow Missile, the Laevateinn Multi-Missile was conceived through a collaborative project between the USC and the ATF during the Terran Conflict interbellum. The warhead consists of highly-advanced tracking systems controlled by the Skirnir's guidance system, enabling the pilot to launch the warhead at extreme ranges. Improvements were also made to its payload - by combining point-singularity technology with antimatter reactions, the warhead creates a small distortion in spacetime after detonation, severely damaging anything within its wake.</t>
		</page>
		<page id="444755" title="Vidar" descr="Vidar" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">Vidar</t>
			<t id="2">(Vidar){20101,65801}</t>
			<t id="3">Ancient by today's standards, the Vidar-class corvette of the AGI Task Force was long superseded by the Vali and eventually the Protectorate-issued Katana. What it lacks on modern ship technology, it makes up with its very high manoeuvrability.\n\nAlthough the design itself is very old, a few Terran engineers have found a way to overhaul the ship to an extent, bringing it almost on par with the newest-generation corvettes. The internal systems are still dated, but upgrades to its engine systems allow it to stand out from the rest of the M-class ships.</t>
			<t id="4">IG M - Vidar Internal Generator</t>
		</page>
		<page id="444756" title="Odin" descr="Odin" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">Odin</t>
			<t id="2">(Odin){20101,65101}</t>
			<t id="3">The first ship to make contact with the Commonwealth after the Earth gate was activated and also the ones to save their fleet from the Kha'ak at Heretic's End, the Odin-class battlecruiser had long been a staple of the Earth Fleet and the AGI Task Force. By the events of the Terran Conflict its capabilities were considered to be highly advanced, being able to stand against destroyers and battleships better compared to other ships of its class.\n\nDue to the events of the Jump Gate shutdown, the Terran Protectorate saw little use for such a heavy carrier, and as such, the Tokyo became the mainstay carrier of their fleets. Several decades of peace would see the former ATF M1 carrier rust away, but fate had another plan for the ship as the gates once again re-opened in 2973. The Odin was then modified to emphasize its heavy carrier role, sacrificing its fighter bays for corvette-sized bays.\n\nUnlike most of the updated pre-shutdown-era ATF ships, it is currently the only one to be sold directly by Terran shipyards. The Protectorate decided that its own Tokyo-class carriers could synergize with the Odin-class heavy carriers and allowed the sale of it to eligible allies of Earth.</t>
			<t id="4">IG XL - Odin Internal Generator</t>
		</page>
		<page id="444757" title="Mobile Mining Base-Ship" descr="Mobile Mining Base-Ship" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">Mobile Mining Base-Ship</t>
			<t id="2">(Mobile Mining Base-Ship){444757,1}</t>
			<t id="3">Based from the chassis of the last-generation Tokyo, the Mobile Mining Base-Ship was the designated deep-space support miner of the Terrans. It served as a base ship for other mining vessels, which would stock minerals into the ship to increase the total payload per run. When the gates shut down, demand for minerals dwindled due to the war economy stagnating, which would see the ship phased out.\n\nWhen the gates re-opened in 2973, it was put back into service with notable changes to its design, a few of which include the capital-grade turrets being replaced with modern L-sized mining turrets and having its docks reduced for greater storage and gas mining capabilities to support the ever-growing Protectorate's interventionist campaign against the Xenon.</t>
			<t id="4">IG XL - Mobile Mining Base-Ship Internal Generator</t>
		</page>
		<page id="444758" title="Woden" descr="Woden" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">Woden</t>
			<t id="2">(Woden){20101, 65201}</t>
			<t id="3">Designated as a possible replacement for the Odin, the Woden was designed to fulfill a flexible role as part-battleship and part-carrier, causing Terran officials to question its capabilities as a dual-purpose capital ship. As the Terran Conflict waned, the demand for such a heavy carrier was not seen. Like the Odin, the next-generation Tokyo would eventually take over both of their carrier roles.\n\nUnlike the Odin, which was revamped into a slightly different role with their redesigns, the Woden kept its purpose intact as an S-ship battlecarrier that could be relegated to battleship duty when the need arises. Boasting several large turrets and a spacious landing area, the Woden could be a force to be reckoned with.</t>
			<t id="4">IG XL - Woden Internal Generator</t>
		</page>
		<page id="444759" title="Shotel" descr="Shotel" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">Shotel</t>
			<t id="2">(Shotel){20101, 61201}</t>
			<t id="3"></t>
			<t id="4">IG L - Shotel Internal Generator</t>
		</page>
		<page id="444760" title="Verdandi" descr="Verdandi" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">Verdandi</t>
			<t id="2">(Verdandi){444760, 1}</t>
			<t id="3">A one-of-a-kind ship built in 2936 by a classified shipwright for a renowned fighter ace, the Verdandi super-interceptor was a high-speed Terran ship capable of performing deep-space reconnaissance of enemy territory and intercepting priority targets in the blink of an eye. Harking back to age-old Terran designs of the 21st and 22nd centuries, it bolsters a forward-swept wing configuration giving it more incredible speed in atmospheric flight at the cost of maneuverability at such high speeds. Zero-G flight fires up all rear engines and thrusters to provide the maximum mobility possible to give the pilot the edge they need in every combat scenario. The ship would, later on, be lost with the Torus Aeternal's destruction by Argon sabotage in 2948, striking a significant blow to the Terrans' recon capabilities on their enemies far from the Solar System.\n\nIn the final moments of the Terran Conflict, the ship's wreckage seemingly disappeared during the initial cleanup operations. A few months later, the ship was spotted flying back and forth the Terran border. It was found to be redesigned with a heavier frame on par with a small corvette seemingly to increase its survivability dramatically. It would later prove instrumental in ensuring the continuity of the ceasefire talks deep in Commonwealth territory with the pilot thwarting the Yaki Syndicate's attempt to destroy the Goner Ozias and saving both Terran and Argon ambassadors. The fate of the original ship after the Jump Gate shutdown remains unknown although a replica is available to citizens in good standing with the Terran Secret Service.</t>
			<t id="4">IG M - Verdandi Internal Generator</t>
		</page>
		<page id="444761" title="Solaris" descr="Solaris" voice="yes">
			<t id="1">Solaris</t>
			<t id="2">(Solaris){444761, 1}</t>
			<t id="3"></t>
			<t id="4">IG L - Solaris Internal Generator</t>
		</page>
	</add>
</diff>